smeidy.info 2018-09-29

# Your Best Source to Login into any Website!

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

## When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site.

## How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

* To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
* To improve our website in order to better serve you.
* To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

## How do we protect your information?

* We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
* We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.
* We do not use Malware Scanning.
* We do not use an SSL certificate.
* We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers.

## Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## We use cookies to:

* Keep track of advertisements.
* Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly. 

## Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

## Third-party links

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

## Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. [Google Support](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en)  
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.  
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy. 

We have implemented the following:

* Remarketing with Google AdSense
* Google Display Network Impression Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

admin at smeidy.info

Last Edited on March 06, 2016.
